(忆往昔)
地狱里有个笼子
There's this cage in hell,
路西法被关在里面  我也曾被关在里面
and it's where they keep Lucifer, and I've been in it.
上帝好像想让我回到那里
I think god wants me to go back.
进入你头脑的并不是上帝  萨姆
It wasn't God inside your head, Sam.
是我
It was me.
你弟弟在地狱
Your brother's in hell...
黑暗  她可是万物的终结
The darkness, she's the end of everything.
我们可以打败她
We can beat her.
和路西法一起
...With Lucifer.
你想要皮囊
You want a vessel?
-不  -B计划
- No. - Plan "B."
有遗言吗
Last words?
你真的能打败她吗
Can you really beat her?
-我可以  -那么好
- I can. - Then, yes.
路西法
Lucifer.
黑暗  她对你来说算什么
The Darkness, what is she to you?
你永远不会伤害我
You'll never hurt me.
抱歉  阿玛拉
I'm sorry, Amara.
我们是联系在一起的  迪恩
We're bound, Dean.
-我告诉过你  -我们会永远联系在一起
- I told you. - We'll always be bound.
我是不可抗拒的
I can't be resisted.
你跟我在一起时  就会有的感觉  是极乐
That feeling that you have when you're with me, just bliss.
你为什么不想那样
Why wouldn't you want that?
你和我将永远在一起
You and I will be together forever.
(如今)
(爱尔兰  科克郡  三十年前)
帕德里克  你干什么呢
Padraic? Oh, what are you doing?
她喜欢这首歌
She loves this song.
只有这个能哄她入睡
It's the only thing that will put her to sleep.
再说
Oh, besides...
这是我们的歌啊
This is our song.
很高兴你又笑了  亲爱的
It's good to see you smiling, mo chuisle.
我在努力  莫拉
I'm trying, Maura.
我在努力
I'm trying.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
那是我们女儿
That would be our daughter.
不是  我听到了...
No. I hear...
尖叫声
a scream.
是...
It's...
撑着  帕德里克
Hold on, Padraic!
撑住
Just hold on!
把它从我脑袋里弄出去
Get it out of my head!
撑住
Hold on!
离他远点
Get away from him!
不
No!
没事了  亲爱的
It'll be okay, sweet.
不会有事的
It'll be o...kay.
[邪恶力量 第11季第11集]
你哥哥被困在炼狱里
When your brother was trapped in purgatory,
你却在这儿泡妞  逗狗
you were here with a girl and a dog.
你赢不了了  萨姆  你不够强大
You can't win this, Sam. You're just not strong enough.
你根本没努力去找他
You didn't even bother trying to find him.
我知道  如果你想击败黑暗
And I know that if you're gonna beat the Darkness,
你得准备好看着你所爱的人死去
you have to be ready to watch the people you love die.
你起来多久了
How long you been up?
我不知道
I don't know.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯  没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
你确定吗  你好几天没出地堡了
Are you sure? 'cause you haven't left the bunker in days.
我没事
I'm fine.
好啊  我好像找到件案子
Well, good. 'cause I think I found us a case.
哈罗德·米勒  65岁
Harold Miller, 65.
橡树公园养老院的住户
A resident of Oak Park, an old folks' home,
昨天被发现死在屋中  头被打碎
was found yesterday in his room with his head bashed in.
但听好了
But get this...
门紧锁  也没有闯入迹象
the doors were locked and there was no sign of break-in.
鬼  恶魔附身
Ghost? Demonic possession?
我觉得值得一看  你说呢
I figure it's worth a look. What do you think?
最棒的是
Oh, and best part is,
橡树公园离这儿就15分钟
Oak Park is 15 minutes from here.
就在我们附近
It's in our backyard.
黑暗怎么办
And what about the Darkness?
小卡怎么办  我们一直没他的消息
What about Cass? We haven't heard from them.
首先  阿玛拉没有丝毫消息
Okay, first of all, we've got zero on Amara.
小卡不会有事的
And Cass... Cass will be fine.
他一向都没事
He always is.
全世界那么多公园
All the parks in the world,
我偏偏选了个有天使的
and I pick one with an angel in it.
我看到你了  简直不敢相信
I saw you. Couldn't believe my eyes.
那就信吧
Well, believe them.
这里真美  是吧
It's beautiful out here, isn't it?
有意思
It's funny.
那些你以为自己根本不会想念的东西
The things you think you're not gonna miss at all,
结果却是你最想念的
you end up missing the very, very most.
趁现在赶紧享受吧
Enjoy it while you can.
我没有恶意  兄弟
I come in peace, brother.
我才不是你的兄弟  路西法
I am not your brother, Lucifer.
我不想打架
Well, I'm not looking for a fight.
事实上  我是击败黑暗的唯一希望
In fact, I am your only hope at beating the Darkness.
我听说
I heard you, uh...
你们这帮熊孩子对她发起了攻击
heard you kids had your big shot at the title,
结果没得手
and you missed it.
不用害怕  兄弟
You don't need to be afraid, brother.
我已经离开了那个讨厌的笼子
I am out of that awful, awful cage.
我是来拯救你们所有人的
And I'm here to save you all.
战神路西法
Lucifer ex machina.
她无法被毁灭
It cannot be destroyed.
但你可以
But you can be!
你们这些基层天使啊
That's the problem with you rank-and-file angels...
毫无远见
no vision.
(橡树公园退休之家  接送服务)
(橡树公园退休之家)
不是吧
Seriously?
这里是个养老院
This place is an old folks' home?
看上去好棒
Looks awesome.
(橡树公园退休之家  早鸟特价  今天就预定你的明天吧)
或许我们该做个预约
Maybe we ought to make a reservation.
能活那么久还好了
Yeah, we should be so lucky to live long enough.
我跟警察说了
As I told the police,
我当时经过哈罗德的房间
I was walking by Harold's room,
听到了很响的撞击声
and I heard a loud banging noise.
然后我还听到房间里的哈罗德大喊
And then I heard Harold yell from inside of his suite,
"把它从我脑袋里弄出去"
"Get it out of my head""
所以我就敲门喊他
So I knocked on the door and called to him.
但他没有回应
And when he didn't reply,
我就用了我的万能钥匙开门进去了
I used my pass key to get into his room.
于是看到了他  他躺着
That's when I saw him. He was on his back.
他的头
His skull was, um...
反正流了很多血
well, there was a lot of blood.
-当时房间里没有别人  -没有
- And nobody else was in the room. - No.
门窗紧锁
The windows and doors were locked.
我还查了安保记录
I even checked the security logs.
整晚没人出入哈罗德的房间
Nobody was in or out of Harold's room all night.
我真不明白怎么会出这种事
I don't really understand what could have happened.
穆尔德
Hey, Mildred.
早啊  亚瑟
Oh, good morning, Arthur.
这是穆尔德  我们一位住户
This is Mildred, one of our residents.
早上好
Good morning.
你总工作到那么晚吗
Um, do you always work late at night?
其实  我最近一直住在这里
I've been, uh, staying here, actually.
我妻子离开了我
My wife left me.
还是用短信分的手  能相信吗
Via text, if you can believe it...
一连串的表情符号
a whole series of emojis.
你怎么做的
What did you do?
我可没忍着  以火攻火了
Oh, I didn't stand for that. Unh-unh. Fought fire with fire.
给她发了大粪符号表情
Sent her the poop emoji.
这也是个办法
Well, that's one way to fly.
我应该发心的  我有时候好蠢
I should have sent the heart. I can be so stupid.
真希望她回我电话
I just wish she'd call me back.
不不  我觉得你做得对
Oh, no, no, I think you did the right thing.
听我说
Um, hey, listen...
由于你经常待在这里
Since you've been staying here, uh, a lot,
你有注意到有什么奇怪的
uh, have you noticed any strange...
声音  气味  或冷点吗
sounds, smells, uh, cold spots?
什么  没有  怎么了
What? Uh, no. Why?
这是例行问题
Oh, just routine questions.
敌人呢  哈罗德有什么敌人吗
Um, what about enemies? Harold have any enemies?
其实
Actually...
他还有不少呢
he had quite a few.
怎么回事
What the hell?
哈罗德在偷其他住户的伟哥
Turns out Harold was stealing the other residents' viagra.
我知道  真混"蛋"  是吧
I know. A real dick move, huh?
我在他房间检测到了电磁场
So I got an EMF hit in his room,
不过几乎每层楼都能检测得到电磁场
but I got an EMF hit on pretty much every floor in the building.
这里死过多少人啊
How many people died in this place?
亚瑟  那个心碎的经理
Arthur, the, uh... heartbroken manager,
他让我查看了所有的住户档案
he gave me access to all the residents' files.
这是所有在这里去世的人
This is everyone who has passed here.
看看
Now, uh...
这家伙  贾克·汤森  跟哈罗德有仇
this guy, Jake Townsend, had beef with Harold,
但不是为了小蓝药丸
but it wasn't over blue pills.
贾克对哈罗德提出过正式投诉啊
Jake filed a formal complaint against Harold?
嗯  据称哈罗德在偷他的养老金支票
Yeah, apparently Harold was stealing his pension checks
自己去兑现
and cashing them for himself.
贾克死后
Now, when Jake died,
他家人向哈罗德发起了民事诉讼
his family filed a civil suit against Harold,
但结果在庭上纠缠
but it just got caught up in the courts
并没能进行庭审
and never went to trial.
或许贾克作为复仇怨魂回来纠缠
So maybe Jake stuck around as a vengeful spirit,
自己解决了问题
took matters into his own hands.
好吧
All right.
那么贾克·汤森葬在哪里
So where's Jake Townsend buried?
(贾克·汤森  挚爱的丈夫和父亲)
哥们
Dude?
你来吧
Oh, you got this.
你来吧  你做得很好
You got it. You're doing great.
不打算退休吗
So no retirement, huh?
是你一直打算
Hey, you're the one who's always wanted
英勇就义的
to go out blaze of glory style...
最好还有邦·乔维的音乐做背景乐
Preferably while the Bon Jovi song is playing.
我是《风中之烛》
I'm a candle in the wind.
是啊  但你说得
Yeah, but the way you said it,
好像英勇就义
it was like that blaze of glory was gonna
会来得比较早
happen sooner rather than later.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
不  其实  我不好  很不好
No, I'm not, actually. Not at all.
再次接近路西法
Being so close to Lucifer again, that...
让我回想起好多
brought stuff up.
我以为已经忘记的事
Stuff I thought I forgot about.
你想谈谈吗
You want to talk about it?
不想
No.
听我说  路西法从未出过那个笼子
Well, look. Lucifer is never getting out of that cage, ever.
而你是永远不会回去了
And you are never going back, period.
所以这事到此结束
So...case closed.
这个案子也结了
And so is this one.
又来查案感觉不错吧
Kind of nice being back on a case, huh?
能换换心情
Get your mind off of things.
赶紧烧了骨头回家吧
Let's burn the bones so we can go home.
(橡树公园退休之家)
回头见  好
See you then. Okay.
你想惹麻烦吗  小姑娘
You up to some trouble, young lady?
总是的  亚瑟
Always, Arthur.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
没有  你没事吧
No. Are you all right?
没事  我们有备用发电机
It's okay. We've got backup generators.
-不是吧  你真没听到吗  -没
- Really? You can't hear that? - No.
像是有人在尖叫
It's sounds like someone's screaming.
那是什么
What is that?
我什么都没看到
I don't see anything.
把它从我脑袋里弄出去
Get it out of my head!
亚瑟  我什么都没听到啊
Arthur, I don't hear anything!
告诉我该做什么
Tell me what to do!
天呐
Oh, my god!
亚瑟
Arthur!
亚瑟说他听到了什么  像是尖叫
Arthur said he heard something, like a scream.
你听到了吗
And did you hear anything?
我什么都没听到
I didn't hear a thing...
只能听到亚瑟拿脑袋撞碎玻璃窗的声音
Except the sound of Arthur bashing his head through that window.
他只想让那声音停下
He just wanted that noise to stop.
他说  "把它从我脑袋里弄出去"
He said, "Get it out of my head."
你还注意到别的了吗  气温下降
Did you notice anything else, a drop in temperature?
没有  但断电了
No. But the power went out.
我从撞碎的窗户往外看时
And when I looked through the broken window,
看到了什么
I saw something.
具体是什么东西
What did you see, exactly?
你不会相信我的  他们是没信
You're not gonna believe me. They certainly didn't.
但我知道我看到了什么
But I know what I saw.
我不是第一次接触这种东西了
This isn't my first brush with something like this.
我10年前就见过鬼
I saw a ghost 10 years ago.
当时也没人信我
Nobody believed me then, either.
我们信你  贝克女士
We believe you, Ms. Baker.
奥斯本探员  谢谢你
Agent Osbourne, thank you.
有联调局在调查我觉得安全多了
I feel so much safer knowing the FBI is looking into this.
这...
Well, that's...
我得需要拿回我的手啊
I'm just gonna need my hand back.
好吧
Okay.
贝克女士  你看到了什么
Ms. Baker, what did you see?
是个女人
It was a woman.
有长长的飘散的头发
Long, flowing hair,
血红的袍子  深陷的眼睛
blood-red robes, sunken eyes,
而且她在
and... and she was...
吃亚瑟的头
feeding on Arthur's head.
很抱歉  失陪一下
I'm so sorry. Um, excuse me one second.
别离开我  奥斯本探员
Please don't leave me, Agent Osbourne.
不不  我们不会离开的
No, no. We're not going anywhere.
打扰  女士
Excuse me. Ma'am?
女士
Ma'am?
抱歉
Sorry.
玛琳  特别探员巴特勒  联调局的
Marlene, Special Agent Butler, FBI.
你知道
Do you know anything
昨晚亚瑟的事吗
about what happened with Arthur last night?
抱歉  我昨晚没来上班
Sorry. I wasn't working last night.
那哈罗德·米勒死的那晚呢
Were you working the night Harold Miller died?
好吧
All right.
谢谢
Thanks.
是  "谢谢"
It's, um... "Thanks."
嗯  当然  抱歉
Right, of course. Uh, sorry.
我就学过一点
I-I only know a little.
我大学时学过一点  过去好久了
I-I took some back in college, but that was a while ago.
大部分人连一点都不知道呢
Most people don't know any.
多谢你努力
I appreciate the trying.
我得继续了
I should probably, uh, get back.
嗯  谢谢
Yes. Uh, thank you.
-证人吗  -不是
- Witness? - No.
好吧  看来  不是鬼
Okay. So, apparently, not a ghost.
不是  鬼是不会吃爆开的人脑的
No. No. Ghosts don't feed on busted-open heads.
嗯
Yeah.
我去验尸官那里问问
All right, I'll check with the coroner,
看第一位被害人脑子里是否少了什么
see if, uh, anything was missing from our first vic's brain.
但愿是僵尸
Fingers crossed it's zombies,
我们就能《行尸走肉》一把了
and we can get our "Walking dead" on.
(不管是什么  我们得查明白)
(赶在它下次进食之前)
知道了  好  再次感谢
Yeah, I got it. Okay, thanks again.
据验尸官说
So, according to the coroner,
哈罗德部分前额叶不见了
part of Harold's frontal lobe was missing.
这符合死亡女妖的特征
And that tracks with banshees.
死亡女妖
Banshees?
死亡女妖不是好的吗
I thought banshees were good.
仙女传说里的是好的
The ones tied to fairy lore are.
他们的喊声是为警告那些将遭遇死亡的人
They cry out as a warning to a victim's impending death.
但这些呢
But these guys...
是坏死亡女妖  一群混球
are malevolent banshees... total dick bags.
他们利用自己的尖叫逼疯猎物
They use their piercing scream to drive their prey crazy.
逼迫被害人自己撞破大脑
Forces the vics to crack open their own eggs,
然后死亡女妖就开吃了
and then the banshees feed on the yolk.
而且只有被害人能听到
Oh, and he only people who can hear the banshee's scream
死亡女妖的尖叫
are the vics.
怪不得穆尔德什么都没听到
Well, that would explain why Mildred didn't hear anything.
而且他们能穿雾而行
Oh, and they, uh, travel through mist,
所以就怪不得能进入哈罗德上锁的房间了
which explains how they got into Harold's locked room.
而且他们只以弱者为目标
And they only prey on the vulnerable.
哈罗德刚做过髋关节置换手术
Harold did just have hip replacement surgery.
亚瑟的妻子刚离开了他
And Arthur's wife just left him.
心碎了
Broken heart.
这也算是"弱"吧
That's a kind of vulnerable, I guess.
他们在一个地带反复作案  直到全吃干净
They hunt the same place until it's picked clean.
而且只晚上出没
And they only hunt at night,
这样我们有几小时可以锁定下一个受害者
so that just gives us a few hours to figure out who's next.
我们怎么杀了它
Then how do we kill it?
金刀  后箱里可没带这个
Gold blade. I don't have any in the trunk,
所以我这就回地堡去拿几把来
so I got to head back to the bunker and grab a couple.
你留下  查明这里谁是"弱者"
You stay here and figure out who in this place is vulnerable.
小卡
Cass?
你在干什么呢
What the hell are you doing, man?
你好  迪恩
Hello, Dean.
嗯
Right, yeah.
我们好几天没你的信儿了
We don't hear from you for days,
你跑来  就搞个天翻地覆
You show up, you start wrecking the joint.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧  你干什么呢
Okay. W-what are you doing?
我在找一个咒语
Well, I'm... looking for a spell,
把阿玛拉引出来  但是
something to draw Amara out, but there's...
毫无发现
there's nothing.
我都看到她了
I had her in my sights.
她受伤了  我本该了结一切
She was hurt. I should have ended it.
等等  什么
Wait. What?
怎么了结
How?
我不知道  但肯定应该有办法的
Well, I don't know. But there has to be something.
我们还能得到几次机会
And how many more chances are we gonna get?
是啊
Yeah, I know.
说要下杀手是一回事
Saying you're gonna kill is one thing, but...
但真做又是另一回事了
actually doing it's something totally different.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我有两次杀阿玛拉的机会
I've had two shots at Amara.
两次都没得手
I struck out both times.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我都不知道从何说起
I don't even know where to start.
迪恩
Dean...
全都告诉我
tell me everything.
进来
Come in.
巴特勒探员啊
Oh, Agent Butler.
-请进吧  -好
- Well, please, do come in. - Sure.
你的搭档呢
Where's that partner of yours?
他...就回来
Oh, he, um... he'll be back soon.
这是你吗
Is this you?
嗯  那是很久以前了
Yes, that was a long time ago.
(致敬佩茜·克莱恩)
那时我还没这么好看呢
Before I got so good-looking.
请坐吧
Please, have a seat.
好
Sure.
-喝茶吗  -不用了  谢谢
- Like some tea? - Uh, no, thank you.
贝克女士
Ms. Baker?
叫我穆尔德吧
Please, Mildred.
穆尔德
Mildred.
我必须跟你说实话
I need to be honest with you.
我和我搭档并非是联调局的
My partner and I, we're not really FBI.
我们是兄弟  我们是猎魔人
We're brothers, and we hunt monsters.
我就知道  我就知道
I knew it. I knew it!
你俩太帅了  根本不像联调局探员
I -- you two are too cute to be FBI agents.
我也知道我多年前看到的那个鬼是真的
And I knew that damn ghost I saw years ago was real.
你看这个
Does this, um...
你看这个像吗
Does this look familiar?
天哪  是的
Oh, my God, yes.
-是个死亡女妖  -是的
- It's a banshee? - It is.
死亡女妖会对被害者尖叫
Banshees scream at their victims,
让他们自残  然后再去吃他们的
getting them to harm themselves, and then they feed on their --
脑子
Brains.
对
Right.
死亡女妖捕食弱者
Now, banshees prey on the vulnerable,
所以我去查了所有的住户医疗记录
so I checked out all of the residents' medical records,
你患有心房纤颤
and you have an atrial fibrillation,
可以用药物治疗
which can be treated with meds.
但这也意味着
But it means that --
我是弱者
I'm vulnerable?
下一个就是我吗
Am I next?
我和我哥哥不会让它得逞的
My brother and I aren't gonna let that happen.
我们会保护你的  好吗
We're gonna protect you, okay?
好
Yeah.
死亡女妖只在夜晚捕猎
Now, banshees only hunt at night,
所以你现在很安全
so you're safe right now.
我们需要你趁现在多休息一下
And we really need you to try and get some rest while you can.
我们会再过来的
We'll be back.
还有一件事
One more thing.
你认识一位叫玛琳的清洁工吗
Do you know a housekeeper named Marlene?
她是聋子
She's deaf.
你们大概是弄错了名字吧
I think maybe you got your names mixed up.
这里的确有位叫玛琳的员工
There is one person on staff named Marlene,
但她休假了
but she's on vacation.
巴特勒探员  我孙女也是聋子
Agent Butler, my granddaughter is deaf,
我真心需要练习手语
and I could really use some practice signing.
如果真有员工是聋子
So if there is a staff member that's deaf,
那我会很想跟他们谈谈
I would love to talk to them.
我也想
So would I.
扮成联调局探员来掩盖你杀人的真相
Dressing up as FBI to cover up your kills?
真是聪明呢
It's almost clever.
我还从没见过这么融入生活的死亡女妖
Never met a banshee that could blend in.
等一下  什么
Wait. What?
我读出你朋友的唇语了
I read your friend's lips.
该进食了
"It's feeding time""
不不  你弄错了  你弄错了
No, no, no, you're mixed up! You're mixed up.
我们不是死亡女妖  我们是猎人
W-we're not banshees. We're hunters.
那是我哥  咱们追捕的是同一样东西
It's my brother. W-we're all hunting the same thing here,
死亡女妖
A-a banshee.
穿着血红长袍  对吧
In -- in blood red robes, right?
我发誓
I swear.
你验证一下  试我一下吧
Look, test me. Test me, please.
看吧
See?
等一下  不要
Wait a minute. No.
谢谢
Thanks.
我叫萨姆·温彻斯特
My name is Sam Winchester.
艾琳·莱希
Eileen Leahy.
你们追捕的那个死亡女妖
The banshee you're hunting...
害死了我的父母
...it killed my parents.
天呐
Oh, God! ?
有个猎人在婴儿床上发现了我  双耳流血
A hunter found me in my crib, ears bleeding.
莉莲·奥格雷迪  这就是她的遗物
Lillian O'Grady, this was hers.
她一直在追捕那个死亡女妖
She'd been tracking the banshee.
但一直没找到
Never found it, though.
这么说莉莲养大了你
So Lillian raised you.
应该说是训练了我
More like trained me.
我16岁时她便去世了
She died when I was 16.
猎魔时牺牲的
On the job?
癌症
Cancer.
那之后你就一直一个人过吗
And you've been on your own ever since?
我喜欢单打独斗
I prefer working alone.
信任问题
Trust issues.
嗯  我懂
Yeah. I know.
那么你妈妈是猎人  还是女巫
So, was your mom a hunter or a witch?
不是  她父亲是个秘密组织的一员
No. Her father was part of this secret organization.
现在已经没了
It's defunct now.
记录者吗
The men of letters?
对
Yeah.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
我和我哥哥
My brother and I...
我们跟你差不多
we're like you.
我们是传人
We're legacies.
我想杀了她的
I tried to kill her.
你们俩似乎通过血印联系在了一起
Well, the two of you are connected somehow by the mark.
不  没那么简单
Yeah, no, it's, uh... it's more than that.
互相吸引吗
Attraction?
迪恩
Oh, Dean.
我知道
I know.
我知道的
I know. Okay?
不管是什么
Whatever it is, a...
吸引  联系
Attraction, connection...
我跟你讲  真的吓到我了
I got to tell you, man, it scares me.
我不知道我能不能阻止它
I don't know that I can stop it.
我都不知道我能不能抗拒它
I don't know that I can resist it.
我也害怕
Hey, it scares me, too.
但我们会查个明白的  我保证
But we will find out what this is, I promise.
最终这或许能帮我们引她出来
In the end, it may help draw her out.
这或许是好事
This could be a good thing.
-萨姆  -迪恩  查一下爱德华·德宾二世
- Sam? - Dean, look up Edward Durbin II.
-等一下  什么  -在记录者的档案里
- Wait. What? - In the men of letters' files.
该死的  她没说谎
Oh, son of a bitch. She ain't lying.
根据记录者的档案记载
According to the men of letters' records,
爱德华·德宾二世于1939年加入
Edward Durbin II was inducted in 1939,
是被派往欧洲的一小支代表团的一员
part of a small delegation that was sent to Europe.
好吧
Right.
(另一个  我要了)
嗯  她父亲当时刚失了业
Yeah, her father had just lost his job.
(高个子归你了)
他当时精神崩溃了
He had a nervous breakdown.
-那他是弱者喽  -没错
- So, he was vulnerable. - Right.
而她妈妈只知道一些基本的咒语
And her mom only knew some basic spells.
她用了一个咒驱逐了死亡女妖
She used one to banish the banshee,
救了艾琳一命
saved Eileen's life.
迪恩  我们在追捕的死亡女妖
Dean, the banshee we're hunting
就是杀了艾琳父母的那个
is the same one that killed Eileen's parents.
真棒
Awesome.
好吧  有什么计划
All right. What's the plan?
我们要用艾琳用来困住我的那个凯尔特咒语
Well, we're gonna use the same Celtic spell eileen used to trap me.
等今晚死亡女妖来找穆尔德时
When the banshee comes for Mildred tonight,
我们就困住它
we trap it.
然后用金子杀了它
And we hit it with gold.
没错
Right.
我不喜欢把穆尔德当成诱饵
I don't like using Mildred as bait.
你在担心她吗
Are you worried about her?
这是不是意味着她真有机会
So does this mean she has a shot?
我确实喜欢《黄金女郎》里的布兰奇
Well, I always did have a thing for Blanche on "Golden girls."
真的吗
Seriously?
别对自己不了解的东西评头论足  萨姆
Hey, don't judge what you don't understand, Sammy.
我没在评头论足
No, I'm -- I'm not judging.
我只是一直喜欢索菲亚
I-I just always had a thing for Sophia.
是啊  我看得出来
Yeah, I could see that.
听着  我不想把任何人当成诱饵
Look, I don't like using anyone as bait.
但我们只能这么办
But this is all we got.
我这就来
I'm on my way.
小卡  我得赶回萨姆身边
Cass, I got to get back to Sam.
听着  我俩谈的事
Listen, about what we talked about,
在我们了解更多情况前...
let's just keep that between you and me...
先别和别人说  好吗
till we know more, okay?
迪恩  那可不...
Dean, that's not --
小卡  相信我就好
Cass, just...trust me.
好吧
All right.
但下次你面对阿玛拉时
But the next time you face Amara,
你不会孤身一人了
you won't be alone.
谢了  小卡
Thanks, Cass.
(关闭  清洁中)
不错嘛
Not bad.
好了
All right.
我猜现在我们只需要...
I guess all we have to do now is, uh...
等着
Wait.
没错
Yeah.
艾琳
Eileen?
你还好吧
You okay?
我很紧张
I'm nervous.
假如这真是我在追踪的那个死亡女妖...
If this really is the banshee I've been looking for...
艾琳  以我的经验来看...
Eileen, in my experience...
复仇并没有人们说得那么好
Revenge is not all it's cracked up to be.
杀死这个死亡女妖
Killing this banshee
并不能带回你的父母
is not gonna bring your parents back.
我从没见过他们
I never met them.
他们对于我而言只是几张照片
They're just pictures to me.
但是...
But...
他们是亲人
they're family.
我的亲人
My family.
我懂的  相信我
I understand. Believe me.
但复仇之后呢  又该怎么办
But after you get your revenge, then what?
我不知道
I have no idea.
我妈妈是个律师
My mother was a lawyer.
能追随她的脚步就挺好
Be nice to follow in her footsteps.
我哥哥来找我去复仇时
I was studying law at Stanford
我正在斯坦福读法律
when my brother came and got me so we could get our revenge.
你俩从那之后就一直一起猎魔了吗
You've been hunting together ever since?
是啊  没有我哥哥的话我不会干这行的
Yeah. I-I wouldn't do this without my brother.
他一直都在罩着我
He's had my back every step of the way.
就算我让他失望时他也如此
Even when I let him down.
艾琳  这是我哥哥  迪恩·温彻斯特
Eileen, this is my brother, Dean Winchester.
迪恩  这是艾琳·莱希
Dean, this is Eileen Leahy.
艾琳  很高兴认识你
Eileen, it's good to meet you.
那么你也是一个...传人
So you're a... a legacy, too.
我猜是的
I guess so, yeah.
对了
Uh, right, well.
我看看
Let's see here.
这是给你的
There's one for you.
我猜你已经有一把了
And I'm guessing you already have one.
那我们就有多余的一把给穆尔德了
Uh, guess we got an extra one for Mildred.
穆尔德去哪了
Where's Mildred?
探员
Agent!
-真高兴你回来了  -是啊
- I'm glad you're back. - Yeah.
我已经觉得安全多了
I feel safer already.
过来  我想给你看点东西
Come here. I want to show you something.
过来坐下嘛
Well, come on and sit down.
我又不咬人  我一直不太喜欢那套
I'm not gonna bite. Never really was my thing.
好吧
Okay.
我在楼上也能看到同样的景色
I have the same view from upstairs.
面西的房间  要额外收费
West-facing rooms, they cost extra.
你得为这景色付钱
You know, you got to pay for the view.
挺不错的
It's not bad.
不错
Not bad.
美人  这景色几乎和你一样美了
Honey, it's almost as gorgeous as you are.
告诉我
You know, tell me something.
你上一次看着落日而不用担心
When's the last time you watched a sunset
夜里有什么东西冒出来  是什么时候的事了
without waiting for something to go bump in the night?
你该找机会试试
You should try it sometime.
是啊
Yeah.
我只希望这不会是我最后一次
I just hope this one isn't my last.
这些东西真的能起作用吗
I mean, does this stuff really work?
死亡女妖出现...你就把手割破
A banshee shows up and... you cut your hand
按在那些符号上
and slap it on one of those things,
然后它就被困住了
and it gets trapped.
真的能行吗
I mean, is this actually something that happens?
能行
Yep.
然后它就会挨上一刀
And then it gets one of these.
穆尔德...一切都会没事的
Mildred...everything's gonna be fine.
好吗
Okay?
告诉我
Tell me something.
你退休之前是做什么的
What did you do before you retired?
我是一支佩茜·克莱恩翻唱乐队的
I was in a Patsy Cline tribute band.
-不会吧  -没错
- No. - I'm deadly serious.
你怀念在路上的日子吗
You ever miss life on the road?
不  不  我玩够了
Nah. Nah, I had my fun.
你想知道快快乐乐长命百岁的秘诀吗
You want to know the secret to living a long and happy life?
我还真想
Actually, yes, I do.
跟随你的心
Follow your heart.
之后  剩下的一切都会水到渠成
You do that, all the rest just figures itself out.
我就是那样做的  我跟随我的心
I did that. I followed my heart.
环游世界  给人们带来欢笑
Traveled the world, made people smile,
让他们暂时忘记烦恼
forget about their problems for a while.
然后我的心说  "该结束了"
And then my heart said, "Well, you're done""
我逍遥够了
I had my fill and...
我退休了
and I retired.
我喜欢这样
And I love it.
这地方并不是我以为的那样
Hey, you know, this place isn't what I expected.
这里的生活好极了
Oh, life here is great.
我想再多享受享受
I'd just like to enjoy it a little more.
你会的  我保证
And you will. I promise.
你的手  还在我膝盖上
Your hand is still on my knee.
我可以往上移
I could move it up.
行了
Okay.
那真是  我要...
That's -- I'm gonna...
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
我什么都没听到  你听到了吗
I don't hear anything. Do you?
萨姆
Sam?
迪恩
Dean?!
萨姆  亚瑟就是这样的
Oh, Sam, it's what happened to Arthur.
迪恩
Dean.
迪恩  看着我
Dean, look at me.
萨姆  它在这里
Sam, it's here!
不
No.
艾琳
Eileen!
-迪恩  停下  -穆尔德
- Dean, stop. - Mildred!
停下
Stop.
(符咒)
你没事吧
You okay?
那么  你感觉怎么样
So... How do you feel?
感觉...
It felt like...
就像普通的猎魔
just another kill.
并没能让我父母活过来
It didn't bring my parents back.
什么都不能
Nothing will.
现在怎么办  念法学院
What now? Law school?
不  这是我的生活
No. This is my life.
如果需要什么  一定联系我
Feel free to drop a line if you ever need anything...
哪怕只想有人陪陪也行
Or even if you just want to hang out.
-不过你不能打电话给我  -好吧
- You can't call me, though. - Okay.
你可以打  但我不会接
I mean, you could call, but I won't answer.
你们俩又要上路了
So you boys hitting the road, huh?
是啊
Yes, ma'am.
这样也好
Well, it's for the best.
反正我们之间也没有未来的
It wouldn't have worked out between us anyway.
好吧
Why not?
亲爱的
Darlin'...
如果说这么多年来
if there's one thing I've learned
我在路上学到了什么
in all my years on the road,
就是看得出一个人对另一个人的渴望
it's when somebody's pining for somebody else.
别再想藏着掖着了
Oh, don't try and hide it now.
跟随你的心  记得吗
Follow your heart. Remember?
我不知道这位幸运的女士是谁
I don't know who the lucky lady is,
当我绝对嫉妒她
but I am damn sure jealous.
我单身  我愿意跟人交往  所以
Well, I'm single, and I am ready to mingle, so...
那你知道我住哪
Well, then you know where I live.
嗯
Yeah.
好了  你们俩乖乖别惹麻烦
All right. You boys stay out of trouble.
不可能的  穆尔德
That's not gonna happen, Mildred.
(他们的背影)
(更可爱了)
小卡走了
Cass gone?
对  我想是的
Yeah, I guess so.
他之前来这里干什么
What was he doing here anyway?
他在找有关黑暗的传说
He was looking for lore on the Darkness.
他有点不对劲
Something a little off about him, too.
小卡总是有点不对劲
Something always seems a little bit off about Cass.
那么近距离面对路西法
Yeah, you know, being so close to Lucifer
可能对他来说也很难承受
probably wasn't easy for him, either.
我们盯着点他就好
We'll just keep an eye on him.
对了  你说得对
You were right, by the way.
重新开始工作  挺有帮助的
Getting back on the job, it... it helped.
等等  再说一次我说得对那部分
Wait. Say that again. The -- that part about me being right.
你这个傻瓜
You're an idiot.
迪恩
Dean...
我和路西法在一起时  他
when I was with Lucifer, he, um...
他给我看了些东西
he showed me things.
就像是我最失败的事情的合辑
It was like a highlight reel of my biggest failures.
是啊  他在搅乱你  他就喜欢这样
Yeah, he was messing with you. That's what he does.
听我说完
Give me a sec.
我应该去找你的
I should've looked for you.
你在炼狱的时候
When you were in purgatory, I...
我应该翻遍每一块石头
I should've turned over every stone.
但我没有
But I didn't.
我停下了
I stopped.
我一直没原谅自己
And I've never forgiven myself for it.
好吧
Well...
我原谅了
I have.
那都是过去的事了
That's in the past, man.
往事已矣
What's done is done.
现在最重要的  一直以来最重要的
All that matters now, all that's ever mattered,
就是我们在一起  所以
is that we're together. So...
少废话  喝酒
Shut up and drink your beer.
嗯  你今晚能入睡了吧
Yeah. You gonna be able to sleep tonight?
嗯  我想是的
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
你呢
What about you?
我脑子里还有点嗡嗡声
Well, I still got some ringing going in my head,
但听点好音乐就能驱走了
but nothing some good music can't wash out.
那个
You know...
我还是不明白
I still can't figure that out.
死亡女妖攻击弱者  对吗
I mean, Banshees go after the vulnerable, right?
那为什么攻击你
So why did it go after you?
你想太多了
You're overthinking it.
它是想攻击穆尔德  看到了我的金刀
It was going after Mildred, it saw my gold blade,
就自我防卫了
acted out of self-defense.
就这么简单
Simple.
嗯  你可能说得对
Yeah. You're probably right.
-我一直都对  -好吧
- I'm always right.  - Yeah, yeah.
-晚安  -晚安
- Night. - Night.
(橡树公园退休之家)